import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

List<Map> QuestionBank = [
  {
    'id': 1,
    'question': 'Your favourite Fruit?',
    'color': Colors.red,
    'A': "Mango",
    'B': "Apple",
    'C': "Banana",
    'D': "Grapes",
    'ans': 'A',
  },
  {
    'id': 2,
    'question': 'How many City is located in Gujarat?',
    'color': Colors.amber,
    'A': "25",
    'B': "15",
    'C': "29",
    'D': "31",
    'ans': 'C',
  },
  {
    'id': 3,
    'question': 'How many State is located in India?',
    'color': Colors.pink,
    'A': "50",
    'B': "31",
    'C': "29",
    'D': "20",
    'ans': 'B',
  },
  {
    'id': 4,
    'question': 'Taj Mahal is located in ___ ?',
    'color': Colors.teal,
    'A': "Delhi",
    'B': "Surat",
    'C': "Bharuch",
    'D': "Agra",
    'ans': 'D',
  },
  {
    'id': 5,
    'question': 'Which Country have largest Population in world?',
    'color': Colors.deepOrange,
    'A': "America",
    'B': "India",
    'C': "Canada",
    'D': "Russia",
    'ans': 'A',
  },
  {
    'id': 6,
    'question': 'Your Favourite Car?',
    'color': Colors.yellow,
    'A': "Bmw",
    'B': "Fortuner",
    'C': "Alto 800",
    'D': "Volvo w8",
    'ans': 'B',
  },
  {
    'id': 7,
    'question': 'Your Favourite Game?',
    'color': Colors.purple,
    'A': "Free fire",
    'B': "Chess",
    'C': "Cricket",
    'D': "Volley",
    'ans': 'D',
  },
  {
    'id': 8,
    'question': 'Biggest Hotel in India is___?',
    'color': Colors.grey,
    'A': "Taj",
    'B': "TGB",
    'C': "Grand",
    'D': "Ganesh",
    'ans': 'A',
  },
  {
    'id': 9,
    'question': 'Owners of TATA Motors is__?',
    'color': Colors.green,
    'A': "Elon",
    'B': "Sundar",
    'C': "Ratan",
    'D': "Rao",
    'ans': 'C',
  },
  {
    'id': 10,
    'question': 'Iphone 13 pro max price in India?',
    'color': Colors.green,
    'A': "10,000",
    'B': "50,000",
    'C': "1,05,000",
    'D': "1,50,500",
    'ans': 'D',
  },
];
